[{"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里", "questionItem": ["4 + 0=", "2+2+5=", "1+3+5=", "2 + 2="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": [["4 + 0=", "2 + 2="], ["2+2+5=", "1+3+5="]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "分类", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里", "questionItem": ["3 + 3=", "2+1+3=", "3 + 2=", "1+2+2="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": [["3 + 3=", "2+1+3="], ["3 + 2=", "1+2+2="]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "分类", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里", "questionItem": ["1+2+2=", "3 + 0=", "3 + 2=", "7-1-3="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": [["1+2+2=", "3 + 2="], ["3 + 0=", "7-1-3="]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "分类", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里", "questionItem": ["7-1-3=", "4 - 1=", "3 + 4=", "2+3+2="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": [["7-1-3=", "4 - 1="], ["3 + 4=", "2+3+2="]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "分类", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里", "questionItem": ["5-1-2=", "6-2-3=", "8-6=", "9-3-5="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": [["5-1-2=", "8-6="], ["6-2-3=", "9-3-5="]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "分类", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里", "questionItem": ["2 + 7=", "7-6=", "4+1+4=", "9-3-5="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": [["2 + 7=", "4+1+4="], ["7-6=", "9-3-5="]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "分类", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里", "questionItem": ["1+2+2=", "7-1-3=", "4 - 1=", "3 + 2="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": [["1+2+2=", "3 + 2="], ["7-1-3=", "4 - 1="]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "分类", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里", "questionItem": ["4 + 5=", "8-2-2=", "4 + 0=", "2+2+5="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": [["4 + 5=", "2+2+5="], ["8-2-2=", "4 + 0="]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "分类", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里", "questionItem": ["4+1+3=", "4 + 4=", "4+1+4=", "1+3+5="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": [["4+1+3=", "4 + 4="], ["4+1+4=", "1+3+5="]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "分类", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "算式分类", "stem": "算一算，将得数相同的算式拖入到相同的框里", "questionItem": ["4 + 1=", "9-1-2=", "1+1+3=", "2+2+2="], "type": "au-equation-drag"}], "answers": [["4 + 1=", "1+1+3="], ["9-1-2=", "2+2+2="]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "", "type": "分类", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-1-08"}]